A Guide to the Rosanna Bencoach papers, 1932-2014
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Political papers, 1960-2014., Extent: 9 boxes (3.825 cubic feet). (Box 1-9)
  - Doug Wilder--campaign for governor, 1989, anti-Wilder material. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Doug Wilder--Governor, 1990-1993, papers. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Doug Wilder--Governor, 1993, Three Years of Change: Governor Wilder's Accomplishments and Vision for Virginia. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Earle Williams--campaign for governor, Virginia Republican Party nomination, 1993, papers. (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Tony Zevgolis--campaign for Congress (4th district), 1992, flier. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Virginia legislative directory, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Virginia legislative directory, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Virginia legislative directory, 2011. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Virginia General Assembly Remembers September 11, 2001, 17 April 2002. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Virginia General Assembly--Carry Me Back to Old Virginny, 1990-1991. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Virginia State Board of Elections videos (2) on election process, 2000, undated. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Gubernatorial Debate program, 1997. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - University of Virginia Center for Governmental Studies and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, The Governors Project--Mills E. Godwin, Jr., Governors Conference, 17-18 July 1998. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - University of Virginia Center for Governmental Studies and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, The Governors Project--A. Linwood Holton Governors Conference, 16-17 July 1999. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - University of Virginia Center for Governmental Studies and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service--Charles S. Robb Governors Conference, 19-20 July 2001. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service--Gerald L. Baliles Governors Conference, 18-19 July 2002. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, Virginia Governors Project--L. Douglas Wilder Governors Conference, 17-18 July 2003. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service--Virginia General Assembly Project, 22-23 July 2004. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, Virginia Political History Project--J. Sargeant Reynolds Conference, 22 July 2005. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, Virginia Political History Project--Virginia Women and Politics, 21 July 2006. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics, Virginia Political History Project--Virginia's Influence on Presidential Politics, 22 June 2012. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics and Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service, Virginia Political History Project--Virginia Women and Politics, 21 July 2006. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - University of Virginia Center for Governmental Studies, newsletter and bulletins, 1999, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics bulletins, 2006-2007. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - University of Virginia Center for Politics papers, 2007, undated. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - University of Virginia Sorensen Institute for Political Leadership Gala Honoring Governor Linwood Holton, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - University of Virginia Sorensen Institute for Political Leadership DVD--Across the Aisle, 2008. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - University of Virginia Weldon Cooper Center for Public Service booklet, undated. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Republican Party convention and U.S. Senate election, 1978. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Republican Party state conventions, 1981-1988. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Republican Party state convention, 16 June 2012. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Republican Party of Virginia plan of organization, 1998. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Republican Party Chairman's Report--Senator Randy J. Forbes, chairman, Republican Party, 1999. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Republican Party of Virginia Regional Training Seminar Manual, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Republican committee for 7th Congressional District, 1978, 1981. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Republican Party of Richmond plan of organization, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Rules of the Republican Party adopted by Republican National Convention, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Republican Party general papers, 1978-1997, undated. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - College Republican Federation of Virginia, 1968-1981. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Young Republican Federation of Virginia consitutions, rules, roster, 1988, undated. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Young Republican National Federation pamphlet, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AARP ad supporting Obama/Biden, 2012. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Creative Direct campaign booklets, 2002, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Christian Coalition voter guide, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Equality Virginia--A Benefit Performance for EVPAC, 1 October 2007. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - James River Republican Women's Club program, 1998. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jennifer Byler Institute and Jennifer and Sarah Byler Memorial Foundation papers, 2002-2003. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Leadership Institute: For Conservatives Who Want to Win--catalog, 2007-2008. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - MBM Consulting Services (M. Boyd Marcus), undated. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Rifle Association 2nd Amendment/Bill of Rights poster, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - National Rifle Association political contributions, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Conservative Grassroots Leadership Conference--2nd Annual Conference, 26 February 2000. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Family Council--Virginia General Assembly report card, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Young Democrats flier, no date. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Exchange, Virginia Correctional Association newsletters, 1996-1997. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Community Highlights, Virginia Department of Correctional Education, 1998-1999. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The Chesterfield Republican, September 1984. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - The Conservative Virginian, December 1979, May 1980. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - The Conservative Virginian, October 1980, Spring 1981. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - New Leadership Report, Fall 1977. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Red State Report, Winter 2006. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - University Republican, 1969,1974, 1978. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Capitol Connections, Summer 1998. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Capitol Connections (guide to the General Assembly), 2011. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Virginia Republican, 1980-1981, 1984-1985, 1988-1990, 1997. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - The Young Virginian, Winter 1988/1989. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Campaign Finance: a Common Cause Analysis, ca. 1988. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - The Baliles Years: A Republican Retrospective, Patrick McSweeney, undated. (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Directory of Public Officials and Government Offices, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Laws of the Public Policy Process, Morton C. Blackwell, undated. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - One-Party Arrogance, undated. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Presidential Hanbook, 1960. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Statement by Delegate John Watkins concerning Democratic Party polling, 1995. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Task Force on Assault Firearms: Report to Governor L. Douglas Wilder, 15 September 1993. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Excerpts from Window of Opportunity by Newt Gingrich, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The Dynamic Dominion by Frank Atkinson, reviews and articles, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Political articles, 1985, 1989, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Political cartoons, ca. 1991. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Governors of Virginia: A Guide to the Capitol's Third Floor Portrait Gallery, ca. 1994, 1998. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brochure and booklet on the Governor's Mansion, ca. 1996, 1999. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Commemorative Collection order forms. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Virginia State Parks meeting facilities brochure. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - American Made Election Equipment catalog. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Aspen Designs order form, the Republican Collection, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Abortion article and stickers, 1993, undated. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Fourth Annual Black History Month Reception: The 9/11 Reminder: America Is One Nation, Under God, Indivisible, 28 February 2002. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Disney America, ca. 1993. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Political map of Virginia, ca. 1993. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Proposed Constitutional amendments (Virginia), 2010, 2012. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Reagan-themed birthday card, 1982. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Senate committees kill pro-family bills, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Uranium--Clean Domestic Energy, ca. 2012. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Constitution Bicentennial, 1987. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Marriage Amendment (Marshall-Newman Amendment), 2006. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - What's at Stake in Virginia, Congressman Newt Gingrich, 21 September 1991 (cassette tape, with Had Enough?). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Had Enough? James C. Miller, chairman, Citizens for a Sound Economy, 28 September 1991 (cassette tape, with What's at Stake in Virginia). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tribute to the late John Dalton, 3 August 1986 (VHS tape). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Conservatives, January 1987 (VHS tape). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - A Different Dominion: Virginia Politics, 1965-1985, ca. 1986 (VHS tape). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Byrd/Howell (VHS tape). (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Button: Who Elected the EPA? from Delegate Brenda Pogge (96th district). (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Pins: The Governor's Commission on Information Technology. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Bumper stickers and door hanger. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Series II: General papers, 1932-ca. 2007., Extent: 1 box (.225 cubic feet). (Box 9)
  General papers, 1932-ca. 2007, consisting of booklets, brochures, bumper stickers, envelopes, fliers, magazines, postcards, programs, rosters, stamps, stereographic cards and VHS tapes and DVDs concerning George Washington, Henrico County, Virginia, historical sites, national parks (Shenandoah and Great Smoky Mountains), Native Americans in Virginia and North Carolina, Philip Mazzei, the Washington Redskins, Reynolds Metals Company, the University of Virginia basketball team, and the Waltons television show.